Diego Moyano

Developer

I am a highly motivated and skilled programmer with a passion for technology. I have a strong academic background in computer science and have been working on personal projects in my spare time to further develop my skills. I am confident that I have the abilities and experience to make a meaningful contribution to your company.



\times	diegomoyano02@gmail.com
-	+5491157300010
9	BUENOS AIRES, Argentina
in	linkedin.com/in/diegomoyan0
0	github.com/DiegoMoyan0

EDUCATION

Licenciatura en Sistemas Universidad Nacional General Sarmiento

06/2020 - Presente

Junior Web Developer Argentina Programa 4.0

02/2023 - 04/2023

Full Stack Web Developer Digital House

02/2023 - 07/2023

WORK EXPERIENCE

Орегагіо

Temporary agencies

2020 - 2022

In various agencies, I performed operational tasks such as inventory management, quality control, and logistical support. I collaborated with the team to meet production goals and ensure efficiency in processes.

MerchantWhite World

2017 - 2019

I managed the daily operations of the store, including customer service, sales, inventory management, and problem-solving. I used effective communication skills to provide excellent customer service and foster long-lasting business relationships.

SOFT SKILLS

Leading and managing projects using Scrum.

Teamwork

Problem-solving

Organization

PERSONAL PROJECTS

- · I developed a web application for a hotel.
- · I am developing a web application for an e-commerce website.

LANGUAGES

Basic Technical English

SKILLS

